Breaking. Israel's Channel 12 says that in case of a U.S. ground operation in Iran, Israeli soldiers will not be participating on the ground.
Israel's News Channel 12 is basically like their CNN.
So, if Israeli soldiers aren't participating on the ground, then what soldiers do you think are?
If U.S. soldiers are operating on the ground, which U.S. soldiers do you think are going?
Well, statistically, black and brown soldiers are sent to the front lines and to higher combat zones than others.
All of you all who have said that Israel and Zionism is not your problem, what do you think it is now?
I keep fucking telling you that this is coming to your doorstep.
And you keep wanting to support people who support this.
And I mean Jasmine Crockett and Hakeem Jeffries and basically all the blacks who are taking all this money.
You think they're going to keep your black son from going to war for Israel?
What you don't know may not kill you, but it'll kill your kids.
It's got to be a better way.